<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Check out all our queens! on Idyllic Ragdoll Cattery</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/queens/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Check out all our queens! on Idyllic Ragdoll Cattery</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <copyright>Designed By [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com/) &amp; Developed By [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/zh/queens/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ayla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/queens/queen_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/queens/queen_1/</guid>
      <description>Alya, our seal bicolor Ragdoll queen, is a striking beauty with strong boning and impressive size, making her a standout in our breeding program. Her robust physique and graceful demeanor exemplify the best qualities of the Ragdoll breed.&#xA;Alya has a playful personality and enjoys spending time with her human family. She loves to chase toys and bask in sunny spots around the house. Her calm demeanor and friendly disposition make her a favorite among everyone who meets her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miya</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh/queens/queen_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh/queens/queen_2/</guid>
      <description>Miya, our stunning seal lynx point-white Ragdoll queen, is a captivating beauty with mesmerizing big blue eyes, a silky soft coat, and a wonderful profile. Miya is not only beautiful but also incredibly affectionate. Her gentle and loving nature makes her a delightful companion and an excellent mother to her kittens.&#xA;We are proud of Miya and the exceptional qualities she brings to our cattery. Her kittens inherit her striking looks, sweet personality, and robust health.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
