<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Check out all our kings! on Idyllic Ragdoll Cattery</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/kings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Check out all our kings! on Idyllic Ragdoll Cattery</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Designed By [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com/) &amp; Developed By [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/kings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/kings/king_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/kings/king_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Introducing Leo, our handsome blue mitted Ragdoll king. Leo is distinguished by his mesmerizing blue eyes and pluffy coat, but it’s his intelligence that truly sets him apart. Extremely smart and curious, Leo loves to explore and engage in interactive play.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Leo also comes from a champion lineage and is DNA tested negative for HCM and PKD. His excellent health, combined with his sharp mind and friendly nature, makes him an outstanding sire for our kittens. Leo enjoys playing in the snow and discovering new things in our large backyard.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/kings/king_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/kings/king_2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Meet Roma, our majestic and handsome king. Roma is a stunning seal bicolor Ragdoll, perfectly representing the breed with his striking blue eyes, luxurious coat, and sweet, gentle personality. He has an affectionate nature and loves to interact with both humans and other pets, making him a wonderful companion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Roma comes from a prestigious lineage of champions and has been DNA tested and certified negative for HCM and PKD, ensuring he is healthy and contributes to the quality of our breeding program. His playful and calm demeanor, combined with his excellent health and pedigree, make him an ideal sire for our kittens.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
